Hi, everyone.
So before we get started, let's take a look at the cost structure for the wireless local area network
that we'll create, which will then use to connect to a society.
I'll start off by taking a very brief look at the impressive dev kits and the related documentation
provided by Impressive.
Will then go through the eclipse idea for the installation process in Windows.
However, if you're using Linux or Mac, you can easily follow instructions within the resources I provided
to complete the installation for you operating system on your own.
And the first task will be to set up a template project which will use going forward and to set up the
project configuration so that we can build in flesh.
Then we'll go through some introductory supplemental lessons for getting our feet wet by taking a look
at how we can set up the example projects provided by expressive and direct provided additional resources
which are helpful in getting started with application development.
Using the SPF index will proceed with some background information on the SPF EDF version of free artus
and go through the Free Artas basics.
Then I'll provide a briefing on the coding style that we'll use so that you know what to expect in the
course.
And it'll also share the location of the Git repository with you.
And from that point, we'll proceed with application development.
We'll create the status slide colors using an LED.
Then we'll create the basis for the wi fi application that we'll build upon throughout the course.
And the lessons that follow will include the initial development of the HTTP server.
And I should mention that the wi fi application and HTTP server will communicate using free are message
queues and we'll expand those throughout the course as well.
Next, we'll move on to the over the year firmware update which works over the wireless local area network
using a mobile device, laptop or any device with wi fi and a web browser that you can use to connect
to your ISP.
32 Dev Kit A.L. Provide boilerplate HTML JavaScript and CSV file templates that we'll continue to build
upon throughout the course.
The application will then be expanded to display data from the DHT 22 temperature and humidity sensor.
And then we'll update the web page and server to enable connecting and disconnecting the ISP 32 with
an access point, as well as displaying the connection information on the web page.
And we'll use non-volatile storage for saving and loading Wi-Fi credentials.
Then we'll implement a wi fi reset button using the boot button on the death kit, which employs the
use of an interrupt and binary semaphore and and PTP time synchronization will be used to display the
local time on the webpage.
And we'll also display the ESP 32 axis point S's I.D. on the Web page as well.
And currently the last section involves a society.
For this section, I'll provide a general introduction to society and our implementation, as well as
some information about account setup and where to find a society resources and documentation.
The next lesson will include some technical background information that is useful to know about prior
to getting into a WSU team will then configure the project so that we're able to connect to a society
core and publish data to and from the MQ test console.
And then we'll do a thorough review of the WC Iot subscribe published source code and updated to publish
the temperature, humidity and the wi fi RSS psi, which is the received signal strength indicator of
the Wi-Fi connection.
And lastly, I should mention that I tested the web page functionality in this course using Google Chrome,
so I suggest that you use the same info about the course organization.
So before starting step by step programming sessions, I'll provide a PowerPoint presentation with relevant
information about the implementation and an overview of general requirements for the programming section.
I'll also provide suggested reading with links to the relevant expressive documentation, and I'll also
outline the steps that we'll go through to implement the tasks at hand with brief explanations of the
selected ESP ADF APIs used for each section.
The provided resources for this course will include the PowerPoint slides.
There you'll find links to the suggested reading and expressive documentation for the APIs that we're
using.
Also, you may want to have this information on hand to review while we're going through the programming
sections, and I encourage you to pause the videos at any time to take a look at these as this may help
you in getting more familiar with this recipes IOT Development Framework.
Also, in each section I've provided you with code that we've implemented, you'll find this in the
section overview if there is an overview for that particular section.
Otherwise I'll include the resources directly in the lesson as shown here.
And in case of any errors, you can always refer back to the attachments provided and compare the code
with yours.
And I do suggest that you type it out as we go along.
All right, so I'll see you in the course.